Privacy Policy
--------------

Blockonomics is a service that simplifies the acceptance of cryptocurrencies as payment for goods and services provided by OneByZero Tech Pte. Ltd. (“**OneByZero Tech**” or “**we**” or “**us**” or “**our**”). This Privacy Policy (the “**Policy**”) helps explain how we collect, use, store, and protect your information when you use our website at [https://blockonomics.co](https://blockonomics.co/), the Blockonomics service or any Blockonomics API or third party applications relying on such API, or any other websites, pages, features, or content related to the Blockonomics service (collectively the “**Services**”). Please read this Policy carefully along with the Blockonomics Terms of Service (the “**Terms**”), which describe the terms under which you use the Services. If you have any questions, please contact us at [webmaster@blockonomics.co](mailto:webmaster@blockonomics.co).

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy**

By accessing and using our Services, you signify your acceptance to the terms of this Policy. If you do not agree with or you are not comfortable with any aspect of this Policy, you should immediately discontinue access or use of our Services.

**Changes to this Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, and when required by law, we will notify you of changes to this Policy. If we make any material changes we will notify you via the email current on your account with us or by means of a notice on our Services prior to the change becoming effective. We may provide additional "just-in-time" disclosures or additional information about the data collection, use and sharing practices of specific Services. These notices may supplement or clarify our privacy practices or may provide you with additional choices about how we process your personal information.

**Scope of this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy only applies to non-custodial Blockonomics Services.

**Our Relationship to You**

For you to understand our data protection obligations and your rights to your personal information under this Policy, it is important that you identify which relationship(s) you have with us. OneByZero Tech has the following relationships:

* A “User” is an individual providing personal information to us via our website or other services, products or platforms, such as by signing up for our newsletter or making an account and posting on the forums. OneByZero Tech is a “data controller” in relationship to its Users.
* A “Customer” is a specific type of User that has engaged us to act as an agent (or, as a “Data Processor”) by obtaining our Services. OneByZero Tech is a “data processor” in relationship to Customers.
* OneByZero Tech does not have a direct relationship with Customers’ End Users. A “Customer End User” is an individual that provides their personal information to Customers. We do not control the purposes or the means by which this personal information is collected, and we are not in a direct relationship with Customer End Users.

Hereinafter we may refer to Customers and Users collectively as “**you**”.

**Information We Collect**

We receive or collect personal information when we operate and provide our Services, including when you install, access, or use our Services. Personal information is data that can be used to identify you directly or indirectly, or to contact you. Our Policy governs all personal information we collect about you and obtain from third party sources. This Policy does not apply to anonymized information as it cannot be used to identify you. Generally, we collect information to provide you with our Services. Except as described in this Policy, we will not sell, lease, rent or loan your personal information to any third party without your prior consent.

Information you provide

* Your Account Information - To create a Blockonomics account, you must provide us with an email address and secure password.
* Your Products and Services - We retain information submitted by you when you create each payment button or donation button, which may include your product or service name, price and description.
* Your Cryptocurrency Addresses - We retain your public cryptocurrency addresses generated in the course of your use of the Service .
* Your Transactions - We retain any records, histories, or metadata for the transactions you conduct on the applicable blockchain. If you request personal information from your customers as part of the transaction, we retain a copy of this information. To monitor cryptocurrency transactions and provide you with account balance information, we store the public keys associated with your private keys.
* Customer Support - We collect any additional information you disclose to our customer support team.

Information we collect from our affiliates

Our “family of companies” is the group of companies related to us by common control or ownership (“**Affiliates**”). In accordance with applicable law, we may obtain information about you from our Affiliates in the normal course of business to provide the Services and Affiliates’ Services to you (e.g., convert cryptocurrency into fiat and make withdrawals into your bank account).

Automatically collected information

* Metrics and Performance Data - We collect service-related, diagnostic, and performance information. This includes high level information about your activity (such as how you use our Services and how you interact with others using our Services), and diagnostic, crash, website, and performance logs and reports.
* Device and Connection Information - We collect device-specific information when you install, access, or use our Services, including your IP address and your web-browser software.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**

Our primary purpose in collecting information is to help us operate, provide, improve, customize, support, and market our Services. We may use your information:

To provide Blockonomics Services

We process your personal information to provide the Services. For example, if you want to use our Services to accept Digital Currency on your website, we require that you provide us with your email address and a password. We cannot provide you with Services without such information.

To provide Service communications

We send administrative or account-related information to you to keep you updated about our Services, inform you of relevant security issues or updates, or provide other transaction-related information. Without such communications, you may not be aware of important developments relating to your account that may affect how you can use our Services.

To provide customer service

We process your personal information when you contact us to resolve any questions, disputes, or to troubleshoot problems. Without processing your personal information for such purposes, we cannot respond to your requests and ensure your uninterrupted use of the Services.

To ensure quality control

We process your personal information for quality control and staff training to make sure we continue to provide you with accurate information. If we do not process personal information for quality control purposes, you may experience issues on the Services such as inaccurate transaction records or other interruptions. Designated Countries: For individuals who reside in the United Kingdom, European Economic Area or Switzerland (collectively the “**Designated Countries**”), pursuant to EU General Data Protection Regulation (“**GDPR**”) or any equivalent legislation (collectively “**DC Data Protection Laws**”), we process this personal information based on our contract with you.

For research and development purposes

We process your personal information to better understand you and, if applicable, your end-users and the way you use and interact with our Services. In addition, we use such information to customize, measure, and improve our Services and the content and layout of our website and applications, and to develop new Services. Without such processing, we cannot ensure your continued enjoyment of our Services. Designated Countries: Pursuant to DC Data Protection Laws, we process this personal information to satisfy our legitimate interests as described above.

To enhance your website experience

We process your personal information to provide a personalized experience, and implement the preferences you request. Without such processing, we may not be able to ensure your continued enjoyment of part or all of our Services. Designated Countries: Pursuant to DC Data Protection Laws, we process this personal information to satisfy our legitimate interests as described above.

To facilitate corporate acquisitions, mergers, or transactions

We may process any information regarding your account and use of our Services as is necessary in the context of corporate acquisitions, mergers, or other corporate transactions. You have the option of closing your account if you do not wish to have your personal information processed for such purposes. Designated Countries: Pursuant to DC Data Protection Laws, we process this personal information to satisfy our legitimate interests as described above.

To engage in marketing activities

Based on your communication preferences, we may send you marketing communications to inform you about relevant product offers and services; to deliver targeted marketing; and to provide you with promotional offers based on your communication preferences. We use information about your usage of our Services and your contact information to provide marketing communications. You can opt-out of our marketing communications at any time. Designated Countries: Pursuant to DC Data Protection Laws, we process this personal information based on your consent or legitimate interest to the extent permitted by DC Data Protection Laws. To the extent we can rely on legitimate interest under the applicable law, we will only send you information about our Services that are similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale or negotiations of a sale to you. You may raise such objections with regard to initial or further processing for purposes of direct marketing, at any time and free of charge. We will not use your information for purposes other than those purposes we have disclosed to you. From time to time we may request your permission to allow us to share your personal information with third parties. You may opt out of having your personal information shared with third parties, or from allowing us to use your personal information for any purpose that is incompatible with the purposes for which we originally collected it or subsequently obtained your authorization. If you choose to limit the use of your personal information, certain features or Services may not be available to you.

**Communications**

We may send you communications that are related to your account or will be related to our Services or information we believe interests you. In the event we send any communication to you which is not related specifically to your account, we will provide you with an "unsubscribe" mechanism through which you may opt out of receiving other similar messages in the future.

**How Your Information Is Shared With Customer End Users**

If you use your account in a transaction with your Customer End User, that Customer End User will have access to an address associated with your public key allowing them to pay for their purchases.

**How We Share Information With Affiliates and Third Parties**

We work with our Affiliates and third-party providers to help us operate, provide, improve, customize, support, and market our Services. For example, we work with companies to provide our infrastructure, delivery, and other systems. These providers may provide us information about you in certain circumstances. We will also share information with our Affiliates in the normal course of business to provide the Services and Affiliate services. We may also share information with law enforcement, government officials, Affiliates or other third parties when:

* We are compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order, or similar legal procedure; or
* We believe in good faith that the disclosure of personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity or to investigate violations of our Terms.

**How We Use Cookies**

When you access our Services, we or companies we work with may place cookies on your computer or other devices. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, and inform us about which parts of our websites people have visited. Please refer to the Blockonomics Cookie Policy for more information about our use of cookies.

**Do-Not-Track**

Some Internet browsers - like Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Safari - include the ability to transmit "Do Not Track" or "DNT" signals. Since uniform standards for "DNT" signals have not been adopted, our Services do not currently process or respond to "DNT" signals.

**Children**

We do not knowingly request or collect personal information from any person under the age of 18. If a user submitting personal information is suspected of being younger than 18 years of age, OneByZero Tech will require the user to close his or her account and will not allow continued use of the Services. We will also take steps to delete the information as soon as possible. Please notify us if you know of any individuals under the age of 18 using our Services so we can take action to prevent access to our Services.

**Access and Modification of Your Personal Information**

You may contact us at webmaster@blockonomics.co to access the personal information we hold about you. If any of the information is inaccurate, you may rectify such information. We reserve the right to limit your access or modifications if your requests are too frequent and/or burdensome. For individuals residing in Designated Countries, please refer to the “International Users” section below.

**Security Safeguards**

We maintain, and require our service providers to maintain, appropriate physical, technical and administrative safeguards to protect the security and confidentiality of the personal information you entrust to us. However, we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse, unauthorized acquisition, or alteration of your data will not occur. Please recognize that you play a vital role in protecting your own personal information. When registering with our Services, it is important to choose a password of sufficient length and complexity, to not reveal this password to any third-parties, and to immediately notify us if you become aware of any unauthorized access to or use of your account. Furthermore, we cannot ensure or warrant the security or confidentiality of information you transmit to us or receive from us by Internet or wireless connection, including email, phone, or SMS, since we have no way of protecting that information once it leaves and until it reaches us. If you have reason to believe that your data is no longer secure, please contact us at the email address, mailing address or telephone number listed at the end of this Privacy Policy.

**Retention**

We limit our retention of your personal information to the only as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes for which we collected it, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting obligations or to resolve disputes. While retention requirements vary by jurisdiction, information about our typical retention periods for different aspects of your personal information are described below.

* Email address for marketing purposes is retained on an ongoing basis until you un-subscribe. Thereafter we will add your details to our suppression list indefinitely.
* Information collected via technical means such as cookies, webpage counters and other analytics tools is kept for a period of up to one year from expiry of the cookie.

Please contact us if you have questions about retention periods for a particular aspect of your personal information which is not detailed above.

**International Transfers of Personal Information**

OneByZero Tech may store, transfer, and otherwise process your personal information in countries outside of the country of your residence. The data protection laws of such countries may not be as protective as the laws of the country in which you reside. To ensure that personal information is adequately protected when transferred outside the Designated Countries, OneByZero Tech relies on Standard Contractual Clauses approved by the European Commission.

**International Users**

This section only applies to individuals residing in a Designated Country.

* Legal bases for processing personal information. Our legal bases for processing are described in the sections above entitled “How We Use the Information We Collect” and “Information We Collect.” We may process your personal information if you consent to the processing, to satisfy our legal obligations, if it is necessary to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts we entered with you or to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract with you, or for our legitimate interests to protect our property, rights or safety of OneByZero Tech, our customers or others.
* Direct Marketing. If you are located in the Designated Countries and are a current customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (email or SMS) with information about our Services that are similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale or negotiations of a sale to you. If you are a new customer and located in the Designated Countries, we will contact you by electronic means for marketing purposes only if you have consented to such communication. If you no longer want us to use your personal information in this way, or to pass your personal information on to third parties for marketing purposes, please opt out of the emails by clicking the “unsubscribe” link in the footer of our email or contact us at webmaster@blockonomics.co. You may raise such objections with regard to initial or further processing for purposes of direct marketing, at any time and free of charge. Direct marketing includes any communications to you that are only based on advertising or promoting products and services.
* Individual Rights. Residents of Designated Countries have the following rights, which can be exercised by contacting us at webmaster@blockonomics.co so that we may consider your request under applicable law.
* Right to withdraw consent. You have the right to withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal information collected on the basis of your consent at any time. Your withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of OneByZero Tech’s processing based on consent before your withdrawal.
* Right of access to and rectification of your personal information. You have a right to request that we provide you a copy of your personal information held by us. This information will be provided without undue delay subject to some fee associated with gathering of the information (as permitted by law), unless such provision adversely affects the rights and freedoms of others. You may also request us to rectify or update any of your personal information held by us that is inaccurate.
* Right to erasure. You have the right to request erasure of your personal information that: (a) is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which it was collected or otherwise processed; (b) was collected in relation to processing that you previously consented, but later withdraw such consent; or (c) was collected in relation to processing activities to which you object, and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for our processing. If we have made your personal information public and are obliged to erase the personal information, we will, taking account of available technology and the cost of implementation, take reasonable steps, including technical measures, to inform other parties that are processing your personal information that you have requested the erasure of any links to, or copy or replication of your personal information. The above is subject to limitations by relevant data protection laws.
* Right to data portability. If we process your personal information based on a contract with you or based on your consent, or the processing is carried out by automated means, you may request to receive your personal information in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, and to have us transfer your personal information directly to another “controller”, where technically feasible, unless exercise of this right adversely affects the rights and freedoms of others. A “controller” is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of your personal information.
* Right to restriction of or processing. You have the right to restrict or object to us processing your personal information where one of the following applies
    * You contest the accuracy of your personal information that we processed. In such instances, we will restrict processing during the period necessary for us to verify the accuracy of your personal information.
    * The processing is unlawful and you oppose the erasure of your personal information and request the restriction of its use instead.
    * We no longer need your personal information for the purposes of the processing, but it is required by you to establish, exercise or defense of legal claims.
    * You have objected to processing, pending the verification whether the legitimate grounds of our processing override your rights.Restricted personal information shall only be processed with your consent or for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims or for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person or for reasons of important public interest. We will inform you if the restriction is lifted.
* Notification of erasure, rectification and restriction. We will communicate any rectification or erasure of your personal information or restriction of processing to each recipient to whom your personal information has been disclosed, unless this proves impossible or involves disproportionate effort. We will inform you about those recipients if you request this information.
* Right to object to processing. Where the processing of your personal information is based on consent, contract or legitimate interests you may restrict or object, at any time, to the processing of your personal information as permitted by applicable law. We can continue to process your personal information if it is necessary for the defense of legal claims, or for any other exceptions permitted by applicable law.
* Automated individual decision-making, including profiling. You have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing of your personal information, including profiling, which produces legal or similarly significant effects on you, save for the exceptions applicable under relevant data protection laws.
* Right to lodge a complaint. If you believe that we have infringed your rights, we encourage you to contact us first at dpo@blockonomics.co so that we can try to resolve your issue or dispute informally. You also have a right to lodge a complaint with a competent supervisory authority situated in a Member State of your habitual residence, place of work, or place of alleged infringement.
* Storage of your personal information. We will try to limit the storage of your personal information to the extent that storage is necessary to serve the purpose(s) for which the personal information was processed, to resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, and as required or permitted by law.
* Data Protection Officer: You may reach our Data Protection Officer at dpo@blockonomoics.co.

Your rights to personal information are not absolute. Access may be denied when:

* Denial of access is required or authorized by law;
* Granting access would have a negative impact on other's privacy;
* To protect our rights and properties; and
* Where the request is frivolous or vexatious.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at webmaster@blocknomics.co, or by mailing us at Blockonomics, 491B River Valley Road, #15-01 Valley Point, Singapore 248371.

Cookie Policy
-------------

Like almost every other online service, our Services (including our website and app) use cookies and similar technologies to provide you with an enhanced user experience as well as allowing us to analyse and improve our Services. We would not be able to provide you with all of our Services, including certain personalised features, without the use of cookies and related technology and as such, your computer, mobile phone, tablet or other enabled mobile device (which we refer to collectively in this policy as a “device”) will need to be set up to enable such technologies.

By visiting and continuing to browse our website, downloading and using our app and using, your Blockonomics account, including, where appropriate, with your browser settings adjusted to accept cookies, you are consenting to our use of cookies, web beacons and related technologies to provide our Services. If you do not consent to our use of cookies your only recourse is to stop using the Services and stop visiting our website. You are also free to disable cookies in your browser, but doing so may interfere with your use of our website or the Services. See Section 2 below for information on how to disable cookies.

**1\. What do we mean when we use the term ‘cookie’, ‘web beacon’ or ‘similar technology’?**

Cookies is a term used to describe is a small text file (typically made of letters and numbers) that is downloaded and stored on your browser or your device by websites that you visit. They are sometimes considered as forming part of the “memory” of your use of websites and related services as they allow service providers to remember you and respond appropriately.

Cookies are typically split into 2 main types, namely:

SESSION COOKIES.

Session cookies are stored in your device’s memory only for the length of time of your browsing session. For example, sessions cookies allow you to move around our website and your account features without having to repeatedly log in. They are not accessible after your browser session may have been inactive for a period of time and are deleted from your device when your browser is closed down.

PERSISTENT COOKIES

Persistent cookies are stored in your devices’ memory and are not deleted when your browser is closed. Persistent cookies can helpfully remember you and your preferences each time you access our Services.

Blockonomics uses both of these types of cookies.

Cookies can also be further categorized as follows:

* Strictly necessary cookies. These are cookies that are required for the necessary operation of our services. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website and/or app.
* Performance cookies. They allow us to recognize and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.
* Functionality cookies. These are used to recognize you when you return to our website. This enables us to personalize our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).
* Targeting cookies. These cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make our website and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose.

WEB BEACONS.

The term ‘web beacon’ is used to describe an object embedded in a webpage or email. This object is typically invisible to you, but it permits us to confirm whether you have viewed the web page and/ or email (as the case may be). There are other names for ‘web beacons’ which you may come across – these include web bug, tracking bug, clear gif and pixel tag.

**2\. Managing Cookies**

You can manage your cookies (including the enabling or disabling of cookies) by using your browser. For example, you block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including cookies that are strictly necessary) you may not be able to access all or parts of our Services.

Each browser is different and as such we suggest that you check the ‘Help’ menu on your particular browser (or your mobile phone’s handset manual) to learn how to change your cookie preference. You may also find more information on how to manage your cookies from third party websites (such as [www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/](https://www.blockonomics.co/views/www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/)).

Here are some links to popular browser cookie information pages which you might find helpful to assist in your cookie management

**3\. General**

We hope the above has clearly explained how we use cookies and similar technologies as well as how you many manage such matters. While we have provided details of third party websites and services which we thought you may find useful, please note that we are not responsible for the content, functionality or services provided by such sites. If you have any further questions or comments about our use of cookies, please contact us via: [webmaster@blockonomics.co](mailto:webmaster@blockonomics.co).

Terms of Service
----------------

**OneByZero Tech Pte Ltd.** (**“OneByZero Tech”** or **“we”** or **“us”** or **“our”**) makes available to users that are merchants certain software services accessible via a mobile device or web application, including Blockonomics (the **“App”**). The App enables users to (i) accept cryptocurrency as a payment method for goods and services; (ii) self custody digital assets; (iii) access reporting and invoicing capabilities; and (iv) additional functionality as OneByZero Tech may add to the App from time to time (collectively the **“Services”**). OneByZero Tech developed these Terms of Service (these **“Terms”**) to describe the terms that govern your use of all versions of the App. These terms and additional information about the App can be found on the Blockonomics website located at [https://blockonomics.co](https://blockonomics.co/) (the **“Site”**).

**Agreement to Terms**

By clicking “I Agree” or by accessing the App or using any or all of the Services, you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you don’t agree to be bound by these Terms, you may not access or use the Services.

**Privacy Policy**

Please refer to our Privacy Policy for information on how we collect, use and disclose information from our users. You acknowledge and agree that your use of the Services is subject to, and that we can collect, use and/or disclose your information (including any personal data you provide to us) in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

**Changes to Terms or Services**

We may modify the Terms at any time at our sole discretion. If we do so, we’ll let you know either by posting the modified Terms on the Site, by providing you a notice through the App, or through other methods of communication which we deem reasonable. The modified Terms will be effective at the time they are either posted on the Site, provided as a notice through the App, or through other methods of communication which we deem reasonable, whichever is earliest, unless we indicate otherwise. It’s important that you review the Terms whenever we modify them because if you continue to use the Services after we have modified the Terms, you are agreeing to be bound by the modified Terms. If you don’t agree to be bound by the modified Terms, then you may not use the Services. Because our Services are evolving over time we may change or discontinue all or any part of the Services, at any time and without notice, at our sole discretion.

**ARBITRATION NOTICE: THESE TERMS CONTAIN AN ARBITRATION CLAUSE FOR USERS IN CERTAIN JURISDICTIONS. IF YOU ARE A USER LOCATED IN THE UNITED STATES OR CANADA YOU AGREE THAT DISPUTES BETWEEN YOU AND ONEBYZERO TECH WILL BE RESOLVED BY BINDING, INDIVIDUAL ARBITRATION IN THE UNITED STATES OR CANADA AS APPLICABLE, AND YOU ARE WAIVING YOUR RIGHT TO A TRIAL BY JURY OR TO PARTICIPATE AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN ANY PURPORTED CLASS ACTION OR REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING.**

**Who May Use the Services**

Eligibility

You may only use the Services if you are 18 years or older and are not barred from using the Services under applicable law.

Registration and Your Information

If you want to use the Services you’ll have to create an account (“**Account**”) via the App. You agree that you won’t disclose your Account credentials to anyone and you’ll notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your Account. You’re responsible for all activities that occur under your Account, or are otherwise referable to your Account credentials, whether or not you know about them. We reserve the right to suspend or terminate your Account if you provide inaccurate, untrue, or incomplete information, or if you fail to comply with the Account registration requirements or these terms.

**Feedback**

We welcome feedback, comments, ideas, and suggestions for improvements to the Services (“**Feedback**”). You can submit Feedback by contacting us at webmaster@blockonomics.co. You grant to us a non-exclusive, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, fully-paid, royalty-free, sublicensable and transferable license under any and all intellectual property rights that you own or control to use, copy, modify, create derivative works based upon and to otherwise exploit the Feedback for any purpose.

**Content Ownership, Responsibility and Removal**

For purposes of these Terms: (i) “**Content**” means text, graphics, images, music, software, audio, video, works of authorship of any kind, and information or other materials that are posted, generated, provided or otherwise made available through the Services; and (ii) “**User Content**” means any content that Account holders (including you) make available through the Services.

We do not claim any ownership rights in any User Content and nothing in these Terms will be deemed to restrict any rights that you may have to use and exploit your User Content unless explicitly indicated in the Terms.

Subject to the foregoing, OneByZero Tech and its licensors exclusively own all right, title and interest in and to the Services and Content, including all associated intellectual property rights. You acknowledge that the Services and Content are protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws of the Singapore and foreign countries. You agree not to remove, alter or obscure any copyright, trademark, service mark or other proprietary rights notices incorporated in or accompanying the Services or Content.

Rights in User Content Granted by You

In order to operate and provide our Services, you grant us a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free, sublicensable, and transferable license to use, copy, distribute, create derivative works of, display, and perform the User Content that you upload, submit, store, send, or receive on the App or through our Services. The rights you grant in this license are for the limited purpose of operating and providing our Services. Additional information about your privacy and how we use User Content is available in the Privacy Policy.

You warrant and represent that you have the right and authority to submit your User Content and that the User Content or any part thereof does not infringe the intellectual property rights or any other rights of any third party.

You acknowledge that, in certain instances, where you have removed your User Content by specifically deleting it, some of your User Content (such as posts or comments you make) may not be completely removed and copies of your User Content may continue to exist on the Services. We are not responsible or liable for the removal or deletion of (or the failure to remove or delete) any of your User Content.

Rights in Content Granted by OneByZero Tech

Subject to your compliance with these Terms, we grant you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable, non-sublicensable license to download, view, copy, display and print the Content solely in connection with your permitted use of the Services.

**Rights in App, Site and Services Granted by OneByZero Tech**

The App, Site and Services are proprietary to OneByZero Tech and its licensors and must not be used other than strictly in accordance with these Terms. OneByZero Tech grants to you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable, non-sublicensable right to use the App and Site for the purposes of accessing and using the Services in accordance with these Terms.

**Fees**

We may charge fee(s) for some or part of the Services we make available to you. All applicable transaction fee(s) are set forth in the applicable fee schedule set forth in **Exhibit A**. We reserve the right to change those fee(s) at our discretion with notice. We also reserve the right to vary or waive the amount of and terms for fee(s) that apply to user(s) of the Services at our discretion in accordance with the terms of our agreement(s) with them.

In addition to the fee(s) specified in **Exhibit A**, you may incur charges from third parties for use of linked services. Third party fee(s) are not charged by OneByZero Tech and are not paid to OneByZero Tech. Please note that we shall not refund any Transaction Fee that arises as a result of you refunding Transactions (as such terms are defined in Exhibit A).

**Acceptable Use and OneByZero Tech Holding’s Enforcement Rights**

You agree not to use the Services (or allow your customers to use the Services) in any way or in connection with any transaction that would (or potentially would):

1. Be considered a “Prohibited Use” or “Prohibited Business”, as further described and set forth in Exhibit B, attached hereto;
2. Violate the terms for a Conditional Use or other provisions set forth in Section 3 of Exhibit B;
3. Violate, misappropriate, or infringe the rights of OneByZero Tech, our users, third parties, or others, including privacy, publicity, intellectual property, or other proprietary rights;
4. Are illegal, defamatory, threatening, intimidating, or harassing;
5. Involve impersonating someone;
6. Breach any duty toward or rights of any person or entity, including rights of publicity, privacy, or trademark;
7. Involve sending illegal or impermissible communications such as bulk messaging, auto-messaging, auto-dialing, and the like;
8. Avoid, bypass, remove, deactivate, impair, descramble or otherwise circumvent any technological measure implemented by us or any of our service providers or any other third party (including another user) to protect the Services or Content;
9. Disguise your location through IP proxying or other methods;
10. Interfere with, or attempt to interfere with, the access of any user, host or network, including, without limitation, sending a virus, overloading, flooding, spamming, or mail-bombing the Services;
11. Involve any unfair, deceptive or abusive act or practice;
12. Violate any applicable law or regulation; or
13. Knowingly encourage or enable any other individual to do any of the foregoing.

Although we have no obligation to monitor any User Content, we have absolute discretion to remove User Content at any time and for any reason without notice. You understand that by using the Services, you may be exposed to User Content that is offensive, indecent, or objectionable. We take no responsibility and assume no liability for any User Content, including any loss or damage to any of your User Content.

You agree to comply with all applicable U.K., Singapore, and other export control and trade sanctions laws (“**Export Laws**”). Without limiting the foregoing, you may not download the App or use the Services if (1) you are in, under the control of, or a national or resident of Cuba, Iran, North Korea, Sudan, or Syria or any other country subject to United States embargo, UN Security Council Resolutions (“**UNSCR**”), HM Treasury's financial sanctions regime, or if you are on the U.S. Treasury Department's Specially Designated Nationals List or the U.S. Commerce Department's Denied Persons List, Unverified List, Entity List HM Treasury's financial sanctions regime; or (2) you intend to supply any Services to Cuba, Iran, North Korea, Sudan or Syria or any other country subject to United States embargo or HM Treasury's financial sanctions regime (or a national or resident of one of these countries), or to a person on the Specially Designated Nationals List, Denied Persons List, Unverified List, Entity List, or HM Treasury's financial sanctions regime.

**Termination**

We may terminate or suspend your access to and use of the Services with immediate effect, at our sole discretion for any reason, at any time and without notice to you. You may cancel your Account at any time by following the account closure instructions in the App. Upon any termination, discontinuation or cancellation of Services or your Account, (i) all rights and/or licences granted to you under these Terms shall immediately cease and terminate and you shall forthwith cease the use and/or access of the App, Site, Services and Content in any way whatsoever; and (ii) notwithstanding the foregoing, the following provisions of these Terms will survive: Feedback, Content Ownership, Responsibility and Removal (save for the subsection “Rights in Content Granted by OneByZero Tech” ), Termination, Warranty Disclaimers, Indemnity, Limitation of Liability, Dispute Resolution, and General Terms.

**Warranty Disclaimers**

YOU EXPRESSLY ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT USE OF THE SERVICES AND CONTENT IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK AND THAT THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO SATISFACTORY QUALITY, PERFORMANCE, ACCURACY AND EFFORT IS WITH YOU. THE APP, SITE AND SERVICES ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS WITHOUT ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY, WHETHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, ONEBYZERO TECH SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND/OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. ONEBYZERO TECH DOES NOT MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES THAT ACCESS TO THE SERVICES OR ANY OF THE MATERIALS CONTAINED THEREIN WILL BE CONTINUOUS, UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, OR ERROR-FREE.

**Indemnity**

You will indemnify and hold harmless OneByZero Tech and its officers, directors, employees and agents from and against any claims, disputes, demands, liabilities, damages, losses, and costs and expenses, including, without limitation, reasonable legal and accounting fees arising out of or in any way connected with (i) your access to or use of the Services or Content, (ii) your User Content, (iii) Third Party Materials, or (iv) your violation of these Terms.

**Important Disclosures and Limitation of Liability**

ONEBYZERO TECH DOES NOT HOLD YOUR DIGITAL TOKENS OR DIGITAL ASSETS. ONEBYZERO TECH IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR

(I) ANY CHARGEBACKS ON TRANSACTIONS, OR (II) THE ACTS OR OMISSIONS OF ANY PARTY WITH WHOM YOU INTERACT, REGARDLESS OF YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES OR WHETHER SUCH PERSONS ARE CLIENTS OR COUNTERPARTIES OF ONEBYZERO TECH.

TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT NOT PROHIBITED BY LAW, ONEBYZERO TECH SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR DAMAGES OF ANY TYPE, WHETHER DIRECT OR INDIRECT, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY RELATED TO YOUR USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE SERVICES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO DAMAGES ALLEGEDLY ARISING FROM THE COMPROMISE OR LOSS OF YOUR LOGIN CREDENTIALS OR FUNDS, OR FOR MISTAKES, OMISSIONS, INTERRUPTIONS, DELAYS, DEFECTS AND/OR ERRORS IN THE TRANSMISSION OF TRANSACTIONS OR MESSAGES TO ANY BLOCKCHAIN NETWORK, OR THE FAILURE OF ANY MESSAGE TO SEND TO OR BE RECEIVED BY THE INTENDED RECIPIENT IN THE INTENDED FORM, OR FOR DIMINUTION OF VALUE OF BITCOIN, ETHER OR ANY OTHER DIGITAL TOKEN OR DIGITAL ASSET. ONEBYZERO TECH SHALL NOT BE LIABLE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES FOR ANY LOST PROFITS OR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, INTANGIBLE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, WHETHER BASED IN CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH AUTHORIZED OR UNAUTHORIZED USE OF THE SERVICES, EVEN IF AN AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE OF ONEBYZERO TECH HAS BEEN ADVISED OF OR KNEW OR SHOULD HAVE KNOWN OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. ONEBYZERO TECH SHALL NOT BE LIABLE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES FOR DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY RELATED TO SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES, AND/OR INFORMATION OFFERED OR PROVIDED BY THIRD-PARTIES AND ACCESSED THROUGH THE APP, SITE OR SERVICES. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR PERSONAL INJURY, OR OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THIS LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN NO EVENT SHALL ONEBYZERO TECH’ TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ALL DAMAGES (OTHER THAN AS MAY BE REQUIRED BY APPLICABLE LAW IN CASES INVOLVING PERSONAL INJURY) EXCEED THE AMOUNT OF ONE HUNDRED U.S. DOLLARS (US$100.00) OR ITS EQUIVALENT IN THE LOCAL CURRENCY OF THE APPLICABLE JURISDICTION.

**Dispute Resolution**

Governing Law and Jurisdiction

These Terms are governed by Singapore law. Both you and we irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Singapore courts for any legal proceedings relating to these Terms. If we agree with you that arbitration would be an appropriate forum, we may joint refer the dispute for arbitration.

**General Terms**

These Terms constitute the entire and exclusive understanding and agreement between OneByZero Tech and you regarding the Services and Content, and these Terms supersede and replace any and all prior oral or written understandings or agreements between OneByZero Tech and you regarding the Services and Content. If any provision of these Terms is held invalid or unenforceable by a court of competent jurisdiction or arbitration tribunal (if applicable), that provision will be enforced to the maximum extent permissible and the other provisions of these Terms will remain in full force and effect. You may not assign or transfer these Terms, by operation of law or otherwise, without our prior written consent. Any attempt by you to assign or transfer these Terms, without such consent, will be null. We may freely assign or transfer these Terms without restriction. Subject to the foregoing, these Terms will bind and inure to the benefit of the parties, their successors and permitted assigns. Any notices or other communications provided by us under these Terms, including those regarding modifications to these Terms, will be given by posting to the Services and/or through other electronic communication. You agree and consent to receive electronically all communications, agreements, documents, notices and disclosures (collectively, "**Communications**") that we provide in connection with your Account and your use of the Services.

**Our failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not be considered a waiver of such right or provision. The waiver of any such right or provision will be effective only if in writing and signed by a duly authorized representative of OneByZero Tech. Except as expressly set forth in these Terms, the exercise by either party of any of its remedies under these Terms will be without prejudice to its other remedies under these Terms or otherwise.**

**These Terms are written in English (U.S.). Any translated version is provided solely for your convenience. To the extent any translated version of our Terms conflicts with the English version, the English version controls.**

Unless otherwise provided in these Terms, a person or entity who is not a party to these Terms shall have no right to enforce any term of these Terms, regardless of whether such person or entity has been identified by name, as a member of a class or as answering a particular description. For the avoidance of doubt, nothing in this provision shall affect the rights of any permitted assignee or transferee of these Terms.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions about these Terms or the Services, please contact us at webmaster@blockonomics.co.

**EXHIBIT A**

**FEE SCHEDULE**

You shall pay OneByZero Tech a one percent (\[\]%) fee (“**Transaction Fee**”), along with any applicable VAT or similar taxes on all transactions that occur using the App through which you accept certain blockchain-based digital currency, app coins, protocol tokens, or other digital currency from your customers (such transactions being “**Transactions**”). The pricing terms set forth herein are confidential and shall not be shared with any third parties.

**EXHIBIT B**

**PROHIBITED USE AND PROHIBITED BUSINESSES**

This policy sets forth the limitations concerning your use of the Services.

1. **PROHIBITED USE.** You may not use the Services to engage in the following categories of activity (“**Prohibited Uses**”). The Prohibited Uses extend to any third party that gains access to the Services through your account or otherwise, regardless of whether such third party was authorized or unauthorized by you to use the Services. The specific types of uses listed below are representative, but not exhaustive, of Prohibited Uses. By using the Services, you confirm that you will not use the Services to do any of the following:
    1. **Unlawful Activity:** Activity which would violate, or assist in violation of, any law, statute, ordinance, or regulation, sanctions programs administered in the countries where OneByZero Tech conducts business, including, but not limited to, the U.S. Department of Treasury’s Office of Foreign Assets Control (“**OFAC**”), or which would involve proceeds of any unlawful activity; publish, distribute or disseminate any unlawful material or information.
    2. **Abusive Activity:** Actions which impose an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on our infrastructure, or detrimentally interfere with, intercept, or expropriate any system, data, or information; transmit or upload any material to the Site or App that contains viruses, Trojan horses, worms, or any other harmful or deleterious programs; attempt to gain unauthorized access to the Site or App, other accounts, computer systems or networks connected to the Site or App, through password mining or any other means; use account information of another party to access or use the Site or App; or transfer your account access or rights to your account to a third party, unless by operation of law or with the express permission of OneByZero Tech.
    3. **Abuse Other Users:** Interfere with another of our user’s access to or use of any Services; defame, abuse, extort, harass, stalk, threaten or otherwise violate or infringe the legal rights (such as, but not limited to, rights of privacy, publicity and intellectual property) of others; harvest or otherwise collect information from the Site or App about others, including, without limitation, email addresses, without proper consent.
    4. **Fraud:** Activity which operates to defraud OneByZero Tech, OneByZero Tech users, or any other person; provide any false, inaccurate, or misleading information to OneByZero Tech.
    5. **Gambling:** Lotteries; bidding fee auctions; sports forecasting or odds making; fantasy sports leagues with cash prizes; Internet gaming; contests; sweepstakes; games of chance.
    6. **Intellectual Property Infringement:** Engage in transactions involving items that infringe or violate any copyright, trademark, right of publicity or privacy or any other proprietary right under the law, including but not limited to sales, distribution, or access to counterfeit music, movies, software, or other licensed materials without the appropriate authorization from the rights holder; use of our intellectual property, name, or logo, including use of our trade or service marks, without express consent from OneByZero Tech, or in a manner that otherwise harms OneByZero Tech or our brand; any action that implies an untrue endorsement by or affiliation with OneByZero Tech.
    7. **Written Policies:** You may not use the Services in a manner that violates, or is otherwise inconsistent with, any operating instructions promulgated by OneByZero Tech.
2. **PROHIBITED BUSINESSES.** The following categories of businesses, business practices, and sale items are barred from the Services (“**Prohibited Businesses**”). The specific types of use listed below are representative, but not exhaustive, of Prohibited Businesses. If you are uncertain as to whether or not your use of the Services involves a Prohibited Business, or have questions about how these requirements apply to you or your customers, please contact us at webmaster@blockonomics.co. By opening an Account, you confirm that you or your customers will not use the Services in connection with any of following businesses, activities, practices, or items:
    1. **Restricted Financial Services:** Check cashing, bail bonds, collections agencies.
    2. **Intellectual Property or Proprietary Rights Infringement:** Sales, distribution, or access to counterfeit music, movies, software, or other licensed materials without the appropriate authorization from the rights holder.
    3. **Counterfeit or Unauthorized Goods:** Unauthorized sale or resale of brand name or designer products or services; sale of goods or services that are illegally imported or exported or which are stolen.
    4. **Regulated Products and Services:** Marijuana dispensaries and related businesses; sale of tobacco, e-cigarettes, and e-liquid; online prescription or pharmaceutical services; age-restricted goods or services; weapons and munitions; gunpowder and other explosives; fireworks and related goods; toxic, flammable, and radioactive materials; products and services with varying legal status on a state-by-state basis.
    5. **Drugs and Drug Paraphernalia:** Sale of narcotics, controlled substances, and any equipment designed for making or using drugs, such as bongs, vaporizers, and hookahs.
    6. **Pseudo-Pharmaceuticals:** Pharmaceuticals and other products that make health claims that have not been approved or verified by the applicable local and/or national regulatory body.
    7. **Substances designed to mimic illegal drugs:** Sale of a legal substance that provides the same effect as an illegal drug (e.g., salvia, kratom).
    8. **Adult Content and Services:** Pornography (including literature, imagery and other media); sites offering any sexually-related services such as prostitution, escorts, pay-per view, or adult live chat features.
    9. **Multi-level Marketing:** Pyramid schemes, network marketing, and referral marketing programs.
    10. **Unfair, Predatory or Deceptive Practices:** Investment opportunities or other services that promise high rewards; sale or resale of a service without added benefit to the buyer; resale of government offerings without authorization or added value; sites that we determine in our sole discretion to be unfair, deceptive, or predatory towards consumers.
    11. **Gambling Services.**
    12. **Weapons Manufacturers/Vendors.**
    13. **Money Services:** Gift cards; prepaid cards; sale of in-game currency unless the merchant is the operator of the virtual world; act as a payment intermediary or aggregator or otherwise resell any of the Services.
    14. **Crowdfunding.**
    15. **High-risk Businesses:** any businesses that we believe pose elevated financial risk or legal liability.
3. **CONDITIONAL USES.** Our express written consent and approval must be obtained prior to using Services for the following categories of business and/or use (“Conditional Uses”). We may also require you to agree to additional conditions, make supplemental representations and warranties, complete enhanced on-boarding procedures, and operate subject to restrictions if you use the Services in connection with any of following businesses, activities, or practices:
    1. **Charities:** Acceptance of donations for nonprofit enterprise.
    2. **Games of Skill:** Games which are not defined as gambling under these Terms or by law, but which require an entry fee and award a prize.
    3. **Religious/Spiritual Organizations:** Operation of a for-profit religious or spiritual organization.
